I'm going to the kitchen pavilion now.
I'll be there!
Please subscribe to our channel!
I'm going to see you all!
I'm off!
Oh, you're so cute!
There's a guy with a cute icon.
What are you going to do? I have to see so much!
Yes, please.
Here I go!
Seino
Six.
Big chance.
Six is up.
Please cheer for sixes, everyone!
Yes, yes, yes!
Here we go!
Yes!
Yay! - Yay!
Yes! Thank you very much!
I got the sticker comp.
Yay!
I wonder what I'll get.
You will have to roll the dice twice.
Twice.
If you get a "zoro-yoko", you win!
What?
I'll roll.
You'll get a "zoro" roll.
Oh, you mean you want to get a "zoro-yoku"?
Yes, sir.
Oh, here.
Yes, please come up
Ah, whoa!
what is it? what is it?
what is it?I wonder.
Oh, isn't it great? You want to know? Anko!
Oh, thanks!
Who is it? Who? Who?
Oh, he's older!
What?
He's old! Yes!
To the Senker.
To the Senker!
But, but, Mono-buri!
Mono-buri!
Thanks!
Are you all feeling okay?
Are you feeling okay?
Are you happy?
Is your throat cute?
Take it easy, stay hydrated and have fun.
I really hope you enjoy the show.
Also, I'm going to be doing my best to keep my voice up this time too.
Is everyone's throat warmed up?
Yes!
From the very first song, I want you to go all out and have fun.
Please enjoy the first song. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Yay!
Se-no!
Here you go!
Thanks for your hard work!
Thank you!
Bye-bye!
See you later!
Good luck at the show!
Good luck!Good luck!
Ooh!
Oh, man!
Tomi!
Tomi-chan!
Stop!
Oh, my God.
It's a pen.
Come on, let's pull it together.
I'll draw this one.
We'll just draw this one.
Ready!
Oh! Oh, man! It's huge!
My car! My car!
This is Port Mac today.
Oh, my gosh!
My car!
Yes! My car!
Oh, man.
Thank you.
I got it.
How was it?
Oh, there's Alice.Oh, it's Alice.
Congratulations!
Hi, Alice.
You're all hot.
Thank you.
It's hot today, so everyone take care of yourselves and have a lot of fun.
Thank you very much.
Yes, live!
Live!
Danielle, Danielle, Danielle, Danielle,
Bye-bye!
We've had a bye-bye-et!
Lots of bad money!
And food!
It was delicious!
I think I got a great one.
Alice!
Anna and Ioni
They stood in line so much!
I was so happy in the heat!
I'm sweating like I've been sweating for a whole show.
I'm standing here and here.
It was so hot!
Everyone's so enthusiastic!
I'm so happy to think that you're going to get even more excited after this.
Thank you so much for waiting in the heat!
It was so close.
It was the first time for me to be that close.
It's a great room!
Thank you for coming.Thank you for coming.
Thank you very much.
I'm going to be at the Yes Performance Chi-Boost Kitchen Car.
It's my first time and I'm looking forward to it.
It's going to be hot, but we're all going to have a great time.
I'm going to have fun.
You can do it again with this.
Here you go.
Bye. - Bye.
Bye.
Ooh!
Congratulations.
I got a towel, too.
Yay!
Thank you very much.
I got it.
I sold at night?
What, five?
You didn't write down your schedule.
I'm sure you'll get the perks you need.
I'm sure you'll get the high score you need?
Yes, I'll do my best.
What? Huh? Wait a minute. It's difficult.
Wait a minute. Harder.
Oh! That's great!
80 points!
Huh? Thank you. But I got beat up too many times.
50!
30 more to go!
One more time! Last dance!
50!
Aaaaah!Aaaaah!
80!
Thank you!
What?
It's me!
I'm a fan of Ogi-chan!
You too, Ogi-chan.
Ogimiru fan.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much!
Ha-ha-ha-ha
A-ha-ha-ha
A-ha-ha-ha!
Ooh!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
He's taking the mud with him!
That's great!
That's good! Go for it!
Come on!
Oh!
Yeah!
Thank you!
Congratulations!
I'm so happy!
Oh!
OgiHanaga is out!
Wow!
Congratulations!
Please.Please.
Thank you but
I'm not a baby member.
It's Mr. Ana.
ua
Ana
Alley
Alley.
I'll talk.
Thank you so much for waiting for me in the heat of the day.
Thank you very much.
Are you looking forward to Piconejoy?
Yes, I am.
We'll do our best to make you have a lot of meaningless fun.
Let's have a lot of fun~!
Have a great time~!
See you on a fun-filled drive!
Thanks for your hard work.
It was amazing.
I could tell that everyone was looking forward to it.
Thank you so much.
Worry everyone.
I hope you drink as much water as possible.
I'm off to Enigee now!
Looking forward to seeing you there!
Yuka!
Thank you for your hard work.
Oh, wow!
Amazing!
Then, it's fun!
Oh!
Oh, my gosh!
Admission acrylic keychain.With an acrylic keychain for admission.
Oh, wow!
This is fun!
Oh, here it comes!
Mine!
I won!
1! 1?
1!
One is the last Mine.
That's four.
Here we go!
Come on!
Wow!
One!
Mine!
Three!
Whoo!
Wow!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
We're in first place!
We got the same number.
I can have the third place!
Thank you!
I really feel like busting down a fence.
Go for it! Go for it!
Whoo!
Wow!
That's great!
Oh, I'm sorry.
That's great! That's great!
Oh, it's all coming together. Are you okay?
Yay!
Oh, my God, you were right.
Thank you!Thank you!
Are you sure? Are you sure?
Hi, Carrie.
Hey, Carrie.
One more time.
One or two of these would be good.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Do you understand?
Yes, I do.
One more time.
Come on.
Whoo-hoo!
Yeah!
Wait, what?
Pressure.
Where's Lennon?
Wait, Lennon's here.
Here.
Come on, Mr. Lennon.
It's okay, it's okay.
Miss Milia!
Miss Milia, Maiditl's Maiditl.
It's Maiditl's Maiditl.
Thank you.
Oh, oh.
Please.
Thank you very much.
Julia and...
What?
Milia!
Are you sure?
You were right, Julia.
Yes! Miss Milia!
Good morning.Good Morning
Good morning.
We're in the middle of the day...
It's a good daylight, you can see a lot... all the way to the back.
Thank you!
Thank you very much.
Good morning.
Thank you for standing in line today.
I hope you continue to enjoy the shuffle party after this.
Thank you very much.
Drink your water.
Please drink water.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Enjoy the rest of the meeting.
I'll do my best. Everybody.
I'll do my best, guys.
Thank you very much.
It was so hot, I was sweating more than at the concert.
But we're going to be at the concert after this.
We'll see each other again after this,
I'm happy, happy.
We're having fun and enjoying ourselves in the heat.
It seemed there were people who had been waiting for us for a long time,
I was really happy.
It was fun.
It already feels like a festival.
Yes, it was.
I could do it during the performance.
That's right.
We did it!
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. Even though it was hot.
So many people came,
Anyway, it was hot, hot in many ways.
But I will see you from now on,But I'm going to meet you now,
To all of you that I just met.
Yes.
You told me to do my best.
I can do my best.
I can do my best. I can do my best.
Thank you so much for coming to see me.
For coming to see me.
I got two Mai-chan.
I was a river girl and a river girl.
And this one.
And I also got Miriyo-san right.
The dice were 66 and it was a zero,
So I called it a "comp prize",
I received the comp prize from Ikolab.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye.